**Eduardo Kawasaki** 

Dear Mr,

I'm a .NET developer (NOC 2174) from Brazil. I'm 31 years old, single and no kids.

I am currently employed in IT company from São Paulo City Hall. In my position as a developer in a software house I deal with all kinds of programming languages and databases. This allows practicing my curious side of always learning something new.

Currently I'm learning a framework called PhoneGap, to develop mobile apps.

Here is a brief description of my experience:

- 10 years of software development experience (6 years in web application - 4 years in embedded systems);

- Excellent skills in C#, MVC .NET, jQuery, CSS, web services and SQL Server;

- Intermediate experience on HTML5 and responsive pages;

- 6 months in PhoneGap framework, generates a mobile app from a SPA (Single Page Application);

I'm used to work in team and work harder to meet goals and deadlines.

Recently I spent one month in Canada (Apr 2016) visiting Toronto, Niagara, Ottawa and Gatineau.

Feel free to contact me for more information.

My online résumé is available on <a href="http://eykawasaki.github.io">http://eykawasaki.github.io</a>.

Sincerely,

Eduardo Kawasaki

## Eduardo Kawasaki

**E-mail**: eykawasaki@yahoo.com **Mobile**: (+55 11) 97102-5983

Linkedin: <a href="http://ca.linkedin.com/in/eykawasaki">http://ca.linkedin.com/in/eykawasaki</a> Skype: eykawasaki

### **SKILLS & COMPETENCIES**

• 6 years of experience developing web applications using MVC .NET;

- 3 years in Web Forms applications (C# and VB.NET) and third-party controls, like DevExpress;
- 4 years in ANSI C programming in embedded systems;
- 3 years using ORM, like nHibernate, Entity Framework and Dapper;
- 6 months in mobile applications using PhoneGap framework;
- Databases: 6 years in SQL Server, 4 years in Oracle, MySQL and PostgreSQL;
- Knowledges: Javascript plugins (jQuery, Bootstrap, KnockoutJS, AngularJS, jQueryMobile), CSS, HTML5, WCF, Windows Service, IIS 7 and Sharepoint;

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Prodam - IT Company from São Paulo City Hall (Oct 2013 to Present)

Position: Analyst Developer

Responsible for develop and maintain all kinds of web applications to São Paulo City Hall employees and the citizens;

- Internet and intranet portals;
- Database: SQL Server, MySQL, PostgreSQL, Oracle and DB2;
- Providing data through web services;
- Scheduling tasks through batchs using Cron Expression;
- Javascript plugins: jQuery, jQueryUI, Bootstrap, KnockoutJS, AngularJS and own framework;
- HTML5, Responsive CSS and tableless;
- Mobile app using Cordova Framework PhoneGap;

# **JBS Group** (Nov 2012 to Oct 2013)

Position: .NET Analyst Developer

Responsible for intranet maintenance (Sharepoint and Web Forms);

- Project Specifications and requirements elicitation;
- Database: only SQL Server (Functions, Queries, Stored Procedures and Views);
- IIS Configuration;
- Web Services and Windows Services;

Woow! Brasil - Online advertising agency (Jun 2010 to Nov 2012)

Position: Junior Web Analyst Developer

Responsible for creating landing pages, corporate websites, Facebook apps, e-commerce, and customization of Joomla and Moodle;

- Management of small projects;
- Integration with payment gateways, like PayPal;

Ingenico Latin America (Jun 2008 to May 2010)

Position: Ansi C Analyst Developer

- Development of applications in ANSI C Language to be used in payment terminals for credit card/debit card;
- Support to developers in all Latin America who use SDK Ingenico;

**DIMEP** - Clock attendance and parking systems (Jun 2006 to Jun 2008)

Position: Firmware Developer

- Development of firmware in ANSI C for control access parking, turnstiles and clock attendance;
- Implementation of serial communication (RS232/RS485) and TCP/IP between the firmware and software through DIMEP communication protocol;
- Hardware Tests;

IAMSPE - Public Hospital of São Paulo State (Oct 2003 to Jul 2006)

Position: Help Desk

- Support to computer users;
- Network administration;

**CETESB** - Environmental Company of São Paulo State (Jan 2001 to Dec 2002)

Position: Data Processing Trainee

- Help Desk;
- Administrative routines;

#### **EDUCATION**

SENAC (Fev 2014 to Dec 2015)

- Specialization course in Project Management PMBOK Guide & Standards
  FIEO (Fev 2003 to Dec 2007)
- Degree Computer Engineering

FITO (Fev 1999 to Dec 2002)

Technician - Data Processing